If you watch my video from last night about my theory, this next video proves it,
and I didn't even know that this Bilderberg meeting took place.
What's a one-world government meeting that rhymes with Schmildeberg?
The Bilderberg meeting.
And it took place in Washington, D.C. this past weekend.
A group of 128 CEOs, prime ministers, journalists, government employees,
notably the Secretary of the U.S. Army, the Secretary of the U.S. Treasury,
all methodically planning the next year.
There were 14 topics for discussion.
The creator of the Bilderberg meeting was a Jewish Freemason, Yosef Redinger.
He literally said that the purpose of the meeting was to orchestrate a one-world agenda and government.
And he tried multiple times to create something like this before creating the Bilderberg meeting.
Fun fact, the meeting was held at the Salamander Hotel in Washington, D.C.
Yosef's nickname during World War II was Salamander.
Just a room full of the most powerful individuals plotting the next year for all of us peasants.
Whatever we think resistance is right now, we are going to have to invent a whole nother version of it.
Hence why your imagination, your wonderment, it has to be engaged.
If you have kids, play with them, not just for them, but for you.
You, me, your mama and your cousin too, we're going to have to step it up by stepping in.
Here we are.